W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Speeches, 1936-1986, undated; 4
  - “Direct Payment Program,” Article for “Cotton Trade Journal”, 1959 April (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1959 March (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Statement on Travel to Interparliamentary Union, 1959 March 27 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - “Direct Payments as a Method of Supporting the Income of Cotton Farmers,” “Article for Cotton Trade Journal”, 1959 May (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Speech on the Agricultural Appropriation Bill to the House, 1959 May 19 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Statement on Taber Amendment to Agricultural Appropriation Bill, 1959 May 19 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Press Release on Management of Waco Veterans Hospital, 1959 May 23 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - “A Progressive Farmer Article,” Tape-Recorded Interview by Jay Richter, 1959 June (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1959 June (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Statement of Secretary Benson on Pending Wheat Bill, circa June 1959 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - “Bill Fixing Friday Preceding Saturday on which Regular Holiday Falls as Holiday for Federal Employees,” “Congressional Record”, 1959 June 30 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Press Releases on McLennan County and Milam County Soil Surveys, 1959 August 17 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - “Extension and Amendment of Public Law 480,” “Congressional Record”, 1959 August 19-20 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Letter on Veto of Public Works Bill, 1959 September 1 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - “Some Aspects of the U.S.S.R.,” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1959 October 12 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Introduction of Lyndon B. Johnson, Delivered at Dedication of National Guard Armory, Cameron, Texas, 1959 October 28 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - “Around the World with Congressman Poage”, 1959 November (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Introduction of Olin Teague at Dedication of Waco Veterans Administration Regional Office, 1959 November 10 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - “Around the World with Congressman Poage”, 1959 December (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Address at Appreciation Luncheon, National Guard Armory, Temple, 1959 December 16 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - “Why I Vote the Democratic Ticket,” Recorded Speech for 1960 General Election (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Press Release on Nominations for U.S. Merchant Marine Academy, 1960 January 5 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Address to American National Cattlemen’s Association, Dallas, 1960 January 28 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Democratic Rally Speech in Dalhart, Texas, 1960 January 30 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Interparliamentary Union Meeting, “The Farmer’s Bill of Rights”, circa 1960 February (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Press Release on President’s Farm Message, 1960 February 9 (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - Press Release on Introduction of Farm Bill, 1960 February 10 (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - “Family Farm Act of 1960,” “Congressional Record”, 1960 February 18 (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1960 March (Box 65, Folder 50)
  - “What of the 1961 Cotton Program?” Article for “Cotton Digest”, circa 1960 March (Box 65, Folder 51)
  - “The Farm Problem,” Committee Print and Draft, 1960 March 30 (Box 65, Folder 52)
  - “Family Farm Act of 1960,” “Congressional Record”, 1960 April 14 (Box 65, Folder 53)
  - Press Release on Family Farm Act of 1960, 1960 April 21 (Box 65, Folder 54)
  - “Twenty-Five Years of Soil Conservation,” “Congressional Record”, 1960 April 27 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Letter of Gratitude to the Eleventh District, 1960 May 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - “Department of Agriculture Appropriations Bill,” “Congressional Record”, 1960 May 10-11 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Press Release on House Committee’s Approval of Farm Bill, 1960 May 18 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - “Farm Problem: One Way to Deal with It,” “Congressional Record”, 1960 May 26 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1960 June (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Remarks to Westview Kiwanis Club, 1960 July 21 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - “The Democrat Convention,” Remarks before Waco Kiwanis Club, 1960 July 26 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - “General Comments on the Farm Problem,” Delivered to Southwest Peanut Growers Association, Stephenville, Texas, 1960 July 29 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - “The Interparliamentary Union”, 1960 September (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - “Soil Conservation,” Article for “Temple Telegram”, 1960 September 2 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - “The Farm Issue,” Delivered at Democratic Midwest Conference, Oklahoma City, 1960 September 17 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Address to Interparliamentary Union Council, 1960 October (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Address to Farm Bureau Meeting, Marlin, 1960 October 13 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Address at Webster City, Iowa Democratic Rally, 1960 October 15 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Press Release on Farm Program, 1960 October 25 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Address at Hale Center, Texas Democratic Rally, 1960 October 27 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Address to Farm Bureau Meeting, Gatesville, 1960 October 31 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - News Release on U.S. Merchant Marine Academy Nominations, 1960 November 1 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Political Radio Speech over K-W-T-X and W-A-C-O, 1960 November 4 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Political Speech for the Democratic Ticket, 1960 November 4 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Radio Speech Delivered in Waco, 1960 November 7 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Address at Southern Methodist University, Dallas, 1960 November 15 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Statement on Appointment to Secretary of Agriculture, 1960 December 15 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - “Report of Congressman W.R. Poage to Constituency”, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - “Financial and Public Support of Soil and Water Conservation,” Delivered to Texas Soil Conservation District Supervisors Convention, Dallas, 1961 January 13 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - “The New Frontier for Rural Telephones,” Delivered at National Telephone Cooperative Association Convention, Dallas, 1961 February 10 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Statement on Move of Farmers Home Association, 1961 February 22 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - “Need for Prompt Enactment of Feed Grains Bill”, 1961 February 24 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - “Adjustment of Funds Available for Farm Operating Funds,” “Congressional Record”, circa 1961 March (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - “Feed Program for 1961,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 March 7-9 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Statement on Sugar Bill, 1961 March 20 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - “Conference Report on the Feed Grains Bill,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 March 21 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Statement on Adjustment of Feed Grain History, 1961 April 12 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - “Authorization for Sale of Agricultural Commodities,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 April 26 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1961 June 12 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - “Introduction of Secretary Orville L. Freeman,” Delivered at events in Rosebud, Temple, and Waco, 1961 June 17 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - “Economic Aspects of Continuing Feed Grains Adjustment Programs,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 July 12 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - Statement made to “Killeen Herald”, 1961 July 20 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - “Agricultural Act of 1961,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 July 26-August 3 (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - Address to Texas Independent Meat Packers Association Convention, 1961 August 11 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1961 August 18 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - “Johnson - Long Right Arm of American Leadership,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 August 30 (Box 66, Folder 44)
  - “The Cattle Brand (Identification) Inspection Program in Texas,” “Congressional Record” and Statement, 1961 September 12-18 (Box 66, Folder 45)
  - “Discrimination in the Peanut Support Program,” “Congressional Record”, 1961 September 12 (Box 66, Folder 46)
  - Press Release on Wayne Speck’s Appointment to Assistant U.S. Attorney, 1961 October 7 (Box 66, Folder 47)
  - General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 48)
  - Press Release on Nominations Deadline to U.S. Merchant Marine Academy, 1962 January 12 (Box 66, Folder 49)
  - “Eulogy of Speaker Sam Rayburn,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 January 18 (Box 66, Folder 50)
  - Statement on Feed Grain Program, 1962 January 23 (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - “Interstate Motor Carriers in Interstate Commerce,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 January 31 (Box 66, Folder 52)
  - “Participation in the 1962 Feed Grain Program,” “Congressional Record” and Letter, 1962 March 22-23 (Box 66, Folder 53)
  - “Eulogy of Congressman Hampton P. Fulmer,” Remarks in Agriculture Committee, 1962 March 28 (Box 66, Folder 54)
  - “Amendments to Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act of 1930,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 April 2 (Box 66, Folder 55)
  - “Remarks on 25th Anniversary of Vice President Lyndon B. Johnson to the House,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 April 10 (Box 66, Folder 56)
  - Statement on Department of Agriculture, 1962 April 28 (Box 66, Folder 57)
  - “Rural Telephone Service,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 May 7 (Box 66, Folder 58)
  - “Transfer of Forestry Nursery Facilities to States,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 May 7 (Box 66, Folder 59)
  - “Marketing of Experiment Station Crops,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 May 17 (Box 66, Folder 60)
  - “Rural Telephone Service,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 May 17 (Box 66, Folder 61)
  - “Sugar Act Amendments of 1962,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 June 18 (Box 66, Folder 62)
  - “Food and Agriculture Act of 1962,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 June 19 (Box 66, Folder 63)
  - “Agricultural Legislation as Seen from Washington,” Delivered to Texas Agricultural Limestone Association, Austin, 1962 June 30 (Box 66, Folder 64)
  - Dedication of the Post Office Building in Temple, 1962 June 30 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - “Is the Elimination of the Farmer Any Solution to the Farm Problem?” “Congressional Record”, circa 1962 July (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - “Food and Agriculture Act of 1962,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 July 19 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - “Interparliamentary Union (and Satellite Bill),” “Congressional Record”, 1962 August 27 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - “Amending Soil Conservation and Domestic Allotment Act,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 September 18 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - “Department of Agriculture and Related Agencies Appropriation Bill of 1963,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 September 18 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - “Federal - State Cooperation,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 September 18 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Press Release on Military Academy Admissions, 1962 September 18 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Statement on Livestock Prices, 1962 September 18 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - “Food and Agriculture Act of 1962,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 September 20 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Address to Interparliamentary Union, Brazil, 1962 October (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - “Wheat Program — Small Farm Exemption,” “Congressional Record”, 1962 October 1 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Statement on Democratic Voting, 1962 November 2 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Statement on Invitation to the Antarctic, 1962 November 13 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Introduction of Governor-Elect John Connally at Dedication of Torbett-Hutchins-Smith Hospital, Marlin, 1962 December 16 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, 1962 December 26-27 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - “On the Death of John Bell,” “Congressional Record”, circa 1963 January (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Address at Private Appreciation Dinner, Waco, 1963 January 2 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - News Release on Appointment of Narvie Caperton as Poage’s Assistant, 1963 January 2 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1963 January 15 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Address to Constituents about Antarctica Trip, 1963 January 18 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Statement on Cotton Market, 1963 January 21 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - “Aircraft Procurement,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 March 4 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1963 March 7 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - “The Present Status of Cotton Legislation,” Delivered to Texas Cotton Ginners, Dallas, 1963 April 1 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Press Release on Coast Guard Academy Examination, 1963 April 8 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - “Feed Grain Act of 1963,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 April 25 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - “On Honorable Fritz Lanham,” “Congressional Record”, circa 1963 May (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - “Interparliamentary Union (Expense Accounts),” “Congressional Record”, 1963 May 8 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - TV Address on Wheat Referendum, 1963 May 10 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - “Continuation of Farm Labor program,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 May 29 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - “Department of Agriculture and Related Agencies Appropriation Bill,” “Congressional Record”, circa 1963 June (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Address to Livestock Marketing Congress, Denver, 1963 June 22 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Press Release on Waco’s Adoption of Federal Offices and Civil Rights Responsibility, 1963 July 12 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - “Comments on Civil Rights”, 1963 July 20 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - News Release on Appointment of Lorena Rural Carrier, 1963 July 20 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  - Press Release on Transfer of Veteran Administration Office to Waco, 1963 August 8 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - “College Aid Program,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 August 14 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - “The Current Attack on the Rural Electrification Administration,” Delivered to Groups in Durham, North Carolina and Houston, 1963 August 14-15 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Address at Stillhouse Hollow Dam Groundbreaking, 1963 September 6 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Press Release on Appointment of Clifton Postmaster, 1963 September 8 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Address to Interparliamentary Union Conference, Belgrade, 1963 September 14 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Press Release on Aid to Skopje, Yugoslavia, 1963 September 24 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - “What Must Be Done,” Delivered at Southern Fertilizer Conference, Atlanta, 1963 October 17 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - “On the Death of Tom Connally,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 October 29 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - “One Year Extension of Mexican Farm Labor Program,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 October 31 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - “Public Works Appropriation Bill,” “On the Death of John Michael Carmody,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 November 19 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - “The Sugar Situation,” Delivered in Hereford, Texas, 1963 November 20 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  - Statement on the Death of John F. Kennedy, 1963 November 23 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  - “The Impact of Politics on Agriculture,” Intended to be Delivered at Texas Farm and Ranch Credit School, Cancelled Because of John F. Kennedy Assassination, 1963 November 26 (Box 67, Folder 50)
  - “Some Phases of the Cooley Cotton Bill,” “Congressional Record”, 1963 December 3 (Box 67, Folder 51)
  - Statement on Report by Comptroller General about Transfer of Veterans Administration Office to Waco, 1963 December 4 (Box 67, Folder 52)
  - Comments on John F. Kennedy, 1963 December 5 (Box 67, Folder 53)
  - “The Role of Government Farm Programs,” Delivered to National Convention of National Farmers Organization, Des Moines, Iowa, 1963 December 5 (Box 67, Folder 54)
  - Press Release on Appointment of Katherine Holstead as Staff Member, 1963 December 26 (Box 67, Folder 55)
  - Address at Appreciation Dinner, Lorena, 1963 December 27 (Box 67, Folder 56)
  - Address at Postal Employees Dinner, Temple, 1963 December 28 (Box 67, Folder 57)
  - “Can Our Congress Remain both Efficient and Representative?” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1963 December 30 (Box 67, Folder 58)
  - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 59)
  - Press Release on Nomination Deadlines for U.S. Merchant Marine Academy, 1964 January 20 (Box 67, Folder 60)
  - Statement on Cotton, 1964 January 29 (Box 67, Folder 61)
  - “Behind Big Lift,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 January 31 (Box 67, Folder 62)
  - “Civil Rights,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 February 8 (Box 67, Folder 63)
  - Announcement of Candidacy for Re-Election, 1964 February 19 (Box 67, Folder 64)
  - “The Development of Farm Policy,” Delivered at Southwestern Agricultural Trade and Farm Policy Conference, College Station, 1964 February 26 (Box 67, Folder 65)
  - “Remarks on Price of Beef,” “Congressional Record”, circa 1964 March (Box 67, Folder 66)
  - “Why Won’t Congress Save the Cotton Industry?” Article for “Cotton Trade Journal”, 1964 March 13 (Box 67, Folder 67)
  - “Our Farm Policy,” Delivered at State Outstanding Young Farmer Banquet, Fredericksburg, Texas, 1964 March 21 (Box 67, Folder 68)
  - “Twenty Years at Texas Research Foundation,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 March 23 (Box 67, Folder 69)
  - “A Review of Pending Legislation: Farm Bill”, 1964 April 8 (Box 67, Folder 70)
  - “Food Stamp Act of 1964,” “The Cotton-Wheat Act,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 April 8 (Box 67, Folder 71)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1964 April 15 (Box 67, Folder 72)
  - “Our Farm Program,” Delivered at Convention of Texas Grain and Feed Association, Fort Worth, 1964 April 17 (Box 67, Folder 73)
  - Letter to Constituents, circa 1964 May (Box 67, Folder 74)
  - “Peanut Research Laboratory,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 May 19 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - “Remarks on Tenth Anniversary of Flood Prevention Program,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 June 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - “National Commission on Food Marketing,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 June 4 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - “The Current Outlook for Federal Agricultural Legislation,” Delivered to National Plant Food Institute Convention, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 1964 June 8 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - “The Destruction of our Federal System,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 June 18 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - “Taking a Hard Look at Our Home City,” Delivered to Waco Kiwanis Club, 1964 July 7 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Statement to House Judiciary Committee on Constitutional Amendment, 1964 July 30 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Statement on Commodity Programs, 1964 August 10 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - “Extension and Amendment of Public Law 480,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 August 17 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - “Increase Federal Housing Administration Loan Fund Limitation,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 August 17 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - “Temporary Retention of ‘1964’ on all Coins,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 August 20 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - “Expansion of Federal Crop Insurance Coverage,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 September 1 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - “Extension and Amendment of Public Law 480,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 September 2-23 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Outline Used in Talking with Schools, 1964 October-December (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - “The Federal Academies,” Press Release, 1964 October 1 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - “Remarks on Carl Vinson and Joe Kilgore,” “Congressional Record”, 1964 October 2 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - “The Spanish Heritage of Central Texas,” Delivered at Annual Picnic at Saint Francis Church, Waco, 1964 October 11 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Political Rally Speech for Harold D. Cooley, Ashboro, North Carolina, 1964 October 29 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Statement on Unsigned Scandal Sheet, 1964 November 4 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - “The Work of the 88th Congress,” Delivered at Appreciation Dinner in Copperas Cove, Texas, 1964 November 4 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - “Agricultural Legislation in the 89th Congress,” Delivered at Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service State Conference, Austin, 1964 November 9 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Remarks at Dedication of Public Library, Temple, 1964 November 9 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - “On the Occasion of Groundbreaking for the Veteran’s Hospital in Temple, Texas”, 1964 November 11 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - “How Agricultural Legislation is Formulated,” Delivered at Farm and Ranch Credit School for Commercial Bankers, College Station, 1964 November 12 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Address at Postal Service Employee Appreciation Dinner, Belton, 1964 November 14 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Letter on Trip to Beirut, Lebanon, 1964 November 16 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Dedication of Draughon-Miller Airport, Temple, 1964 December 11 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - “The Future of Our Farm Programs,” Delivered at Farm and Ranch Club, Temple, 1964 December 11 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - “Remarks on the Annual Meeting of the American Interparliamentary Union,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 January 13 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Press Release on U.S. Merchant Marine Academy Nominations, 1965 January 23 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - “Aid to the United Arab Republic,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 January 26 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - “Do We Really Want Efficiency and Economy in the Veterans’ Administration,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 February 1 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Statement on the President’s Farm Message, Release on East Waco Turkey Processing Plant, 1965 February 4-5 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Address at Testimonial Dinner, Gatesville, 1965 February 13 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - “The Future of Farm Programs,” Delivered at Texas Federation of Cooperatives, Houston, 1965 February 15 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Address at Dining-In Program of the 366th Navigator Training Squadron, James Connally Air Force Base, 1965 February 26 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - “Federal Intermediate Credit Banks,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 March 15 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - “Increase Federal Housing Administration Loan Fund Limitation,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 March 15 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - “A ‘Without Recourse’ Guess on Future Farm Programs,” Delivered at Texas Cotton Association Meeting, Dallas, 1965 March 19 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - “A Guess at the Future of Our Farm Programs,” Delivered at Pure Milk Association Meeting, Chicago, 1965 March 20 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - “Poage Proposes Profit-Making Land Retirement Program,” Press Release, 1965 March 20 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - Statements and Releases, 1956 April (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1965 May 5 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - Statement on Project Head Start, 1965 May 18 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1965 June (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - “The President’s Speech at Baylor,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 June 3 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - Press Releases, 1965 June 22 (Box 68, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence on H.R. 9811, 1965 July (Box 68, Folder 49)
  - Press Release on James Connally Technical Institute Grant, 1965 July 28 (Box 68, Folder 50)
  - “Food and Agriculture Act of 1965,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 August 17-19 (Box 68, Folder 51)
  - “Assistance to (Connally and Robinson) Public Schools,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 August 30 (Box 68, Folder 52)
  - Dedication of Waco Dam, 1965 September 4 (Box 68, Folder 53)
  - “Disregard for Law,” Delivered at Pythian Homecoming, Weatherford, Texas, 1965 September 5 (Box 68, Folder 54)
  - Address at Appreciation dinner, Westphalia, Texas, 1965 September 4 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  - “New Prospects for International Economic Relations,” Delivered at 54th Interparliamentary Conference, Ottawa, Canada, 1965 September 14 (Box 68, Folder 56)
  - “Amending the Consolidated Farmers Home Administration Act of 1961,” “Congressional Record”, 1965 September 23 (Box 68, Folder 57)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1965 October (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Statement on Travel and Press Release on U.S. Department of Agriculture Pecan Announcement, 1965 November (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - “Some of Our Foreign Problems,” Delivered at Temple United Civics Club, 1965 December 1 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - “The Vietnam War,” Delivered to Killeen United Civics Club, 1965 December 6 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Remarks at Appreciation Day Dinner for Graham Purcell, Wichita Falls, 1965 December 8 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Address to Temple Farm and Ranch Club, 1965 December 10 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - “The American Home Front,” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1965 December 13 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - “Our American Farm Program,” Delivered at Appreciation Dinner, Marlin, 1965 December 13 (Box 69, Folder 8)